[IN TONY'S VOICE]
No, I ain't, Mrs. Torrance.
[PHONE RINGING]
DOCTOR: Now, hold your eyes still
so I can see.
WENDY:
When was the Overlook built?
BOTH:
Yes.
WENDY: Oh, no!
DANNY: Keep America clean.
DANNY:
I won't, Mom.
...because I'm going to
make lunch soon.
-Okay?
DANNY: Okay, Mom.
MAN [ON RECORDING]: We're sorry.
Your call cannot be completed as dialed.
NOBODY: This is a poorly made subtitle.
Subtitles should not have more than 2 lines,
but fixing this automatically is very hard.
NOBODY: Let's see if this awful regex
also works with 2 people in the same subtitle.
SOMEBODY: Yeah, let's!
This tool has
one purpose, and one purpose only:
To obliterate crappy SRT files.