It requires
double authentication.
Which one?
[OBRUCHEV] Him.
Hardy. Hardy! Don't let them.
Don't let them.
Don't let them, please.
- [WOMAN SCREAMS]
- [GUNFIRE]
[DEVICE BEEPING]
[LOCKS CLICKING OPEN]
[AIR HISSING]
[DEVICE BEEPS]
- [BODY THUDS]
- Oh.
[MAN ON PA] Warning,
facility lockdown in progress.
- All exits are now sealed.
- [ALARM BLARING]
Warning,
facility lockdown in progress.
All exits are now sealed.
Oh, what is, uh...
It's a safety belt? This?
Wow.
I... I cannot!
There is no elevator!
[SCREAMING]
[GASPS]
Magnets. [SCREAMS]
- [BEEPS]
- [EXPLOSIONS]
Sir, I've just received
the most unusual...
I've seen it.
[WHIRRING]
Oh, Jesus Christ.
Sir, what's
the Heracles project?
- [SIGHS]
- This lab isn't on the books.
No, it's not.