Hi. l've got an appointment
with Mr. Ullman.
My name is Jack Torrance.
His office is the first door
on the left.
Thank you.
[KNOCKS]
-Mr. Ullman?
-Yes.
-I'm Jack Torrance.
-Oh, come on in, Jack.
-Very nice to meet you.
-Nice to meet you.
-This is my secretary, Susie.
-Hello.
-Susie, how do you do?
-Any trouble finding us?
No problem at all.
l made the trip in 3 1/2 hours.
That's very good time.
Sit down a minute, Jack.
Just make yourself at home.
Like some coffee?
lf you're having some,
l wouldn't mind. Thanks.
-Susie.
-Sure.
And ask Bill Watson to join us.
Yes, l will.
[MUSlC PLAYS ON TV]
Mom?
Yeah?
Do you really want to go and live
in that hotel for the winter?
Sure I do.
lt'll be lots of fun.
Yeah. l guess so.
Anyway, there's hardly anybody
to play with around here.
l know. It always takes
a little time to make new friends.
Yeah, l guess so.
What about Tony?
He's looking forward
to the hotel, l bet.
[lN TONY'S VOlCE]
No, l ain't, Mrs. Torrance.
Now, come on, Tony.
Don't be silly.
l don't want to go there.
How come you don't want to go?
l just don't.
Let's just wait and see.
We're all going to have
a real good time.
Bill, I'd like you
to meet Jack Torrance.
How do you do, Bill?
-Nice to meet you.
-Pleasure to meet you.
Grab a chair, Bill. Join in.
Jack is going to take care of
the Overlook for us this winter.
l'd like you to take him around
soon as we're through.
Fine.
Jack is a schoolteacher.
Uh, formerly a schoolteacher.
BILL:
What line of work are you in now?
l'm a writer.
Teaching's been more or less
a way of making ends meet.
This ought to be
quite a change for you.
Well, I'm looking for a change.
Our people in Denver recommended
Jack very highly, and for once...
...l agree with them.
Let's see, where were we?
l was about to explain...
...that our season here runs from
May 1 5th to October 30th.
Then we close down completely
until the following May.
Do you mind if l ask why you do that?
lt seems to me that the skiing
up here would be fantastic.
lt would be. The problem is
the enormous cost...
...it would be to keep
the road to Sidewinder open.
lt's a 25-mile stretch of road.
lt gets 20 feet of snow
during the winter.
There's just no way to make it
economically feasible...
...to keep it clear.
When the place was built in 1 907...
...there was very little interest
in winter sports.
This site was chosen for its
seclusion and scenic beauty.
lt's certainly got plenty of that.
That's right.
Did they give you any idea in Denver...
...about what the job entails?
Only in a very general way.
Well...
...the winters can be fantastically cruel.
The basic idea is to cope
with the very costly damage...
...and depreciation
which can occur.
This consists mainly
of running the boiler...
...heating different parts of the
hotel on a daily rotating basis...
...repairing damage as it occurs...
...and doing repairs so the
elements can't get a foothold.
That sounds fine to me.
Physically, it's not
a very demanding job.
The only thing that can get a bit
trying here during the winter...
...is a tremendous sense
of isolation.
That just happens to be
exactly what l'm looking for.
l'm outlining a new writing project.
Five months of peace
is just what I want.
That's very good, Jack.
Because, for some people...
...solitude...
...and isolation...
...can, of itself, become a problem.
Not for me.
How about your wife and son?
Do you think they'll take to it?
They'll love it.
Great.
Well, before l turn you over to Bill...
...there's one other thing l think
we should talk about.
Not to sound melodramatic...
...but it's been known to
give a few people...
...second thoughts about the job.
l'm intrigued.
l don't suppose they
said anything in Denver...
...about the tragedy we had up here
during the winter of 1 970.
l don't believe they did.
ULLMAN:
Well....
My predecessor in this job...
...hired a man named Charles Grady
as the winter caretaker.
He came up with his wife and
two little girls of about 8 and 1 0.
He had a good employment record,
good references.
And from what l've been told,
he seemed...
...like a completely
normal individual.
But at some point during the winter...
...he must have suffered some kind
of a complete mental breakdown.
He ran amuck...
...and killed his family
with an ax.
Stacked them neatly in a room
in the west wing, and then...
...he put both barrels
of his shotgun in his mouth.
The police thought...
...that it was what the old-timers
used to call cabin fever.
A kind of claustrophobic reaction
which can occur...
...when people are shut in together
over long periods of time.
Wow.
That is...
...quite a story.
Yeah, it is.
lt's still hard for me to believe
it actually happened here.
But it did.
And, uh...
...l think you can appreciate
why I wanted to tell you about it.
l certainly can.
l also understand
why your people in Denver...
...left it for you to tell me.
Obviously, some people
can be put off...
...from staying in a place where
something like that happened.
You can rest assured that's not
going to happen with me.
And as far as my wife
is concerned...
...l'm sure she'll be absolutely
fascinated when l tell her.
She's a confirmed ghost story...
...and horror film addict.
Tony, do you think Dad'll get the job?
He already did.
He's going to phone Wendy up
in a few minutes to tell her.
[PHONE RlNGlNG]
Hello.
-Hi, babe.
-Hi, hon. How's it going?
Great. l'm at the hotel and
l still have a lot to go through.
l don't think l can get home
before 9:00 or 1 0:00.
Sounds like you got the job.
Right. lt's a beautiful place.
You and Danny are going to love it.
Tony, why don't you want to go
to the hotel?
l don't know.
You do too know.
Now come on, tell me.
l don't want to.
Please.
No.
Now, Tony, tell me.
DOCTOR: Now, hold your eyes still
so l can see.
That's good. Now the other one.
Good boy.
Now, Danny...
...when you were brushing
your teeth...
...do you remember if you
smelled anything funny...
...or saw any bright, flashing
lights or anything at all strange?
No.
DOCTOR: Do you remember
when you were brushing your teeth?
Yes.
What's the next thing you remember
after you were brushing your teeth?
My mom was saying, "Wake up.
Wake up, Danny, wake up."
Now, Danny, can you remember
what you were doing...
...just before you started
brushing your teeth?
Talking to Tony.
ls Tony one of your animals?
No. He's a little boy
that lives in my mouth.
Tony's his imaginary friend.
DOCTOR:
Oh.
lf you were to open your mouth now,
could l see Tony?
No.
Why not?
Because he hides.
Where does he go?
To my stomach.
Does Tony ever tell you
to do things?
l don't want to talk
about Tony anymore.
Okay.
That's fine.
All right, Danny.
l'm going to ask you
to do me a favor...
...and stay quietly in bed
for the rest of the day. Okay?
Do l have to?
Yes. l'd like you to.
We're going in the other room
for a few minutes and talk.
l'll come back and check on you.
-Okay.
-Bye.
-Shall we go into the living room?
-Yes.
-Please.
-Thank you.
Mrs. Torrance, I don't think
you have anything to worry about.
l'm quite sure there's nothing
physically wrong with Danny.
Yeah?
Oh.
He seems absolutely fine now.
But you should've seen him.
l know.
Kids can scare you to death.
But believe me, these episodes
are not at all uncommon.
And they look much worse
than they are.
But what was the matter with him?
Most of the time, these episodes
with kids are never explained.
They're brought on by emotional
factors and rarely occur again.
They're more akin
to autohypnosis...
...a kind of self-induced trance.
lf it reoccurs, which l doubt...
...we can always think about
having some tests done.
No, thank you.
l'm sure you're right.
Have you been in Boulder long?
Only about three months.
We're from Vermont. My husband
was teaching school there.
Did the appearance
of Danny's imaginary friend....
Tony.
Did Tony's first appearance happen
to coincide with your arrival here?
No, um....
Let's see....
l guess Danny started
talking to Tony...
...about the time we put him
in nursery school.
Did he adjust well to school?
No.
He didn't like it too much at first.
Then he had an injury, so we kept
him out for a while and....
Yeah, l guess that's about when l first
noticed he was talking to Tony.
What sort of injury did he have?
He dislocated his shoulder.
How did he manage to do that?
lt was just one of
those things, you know.
Purely an accident.
My husband had been drinking...
...and he came home
about three hours late.
So he wasn't exactly
in the greatest mood that night.
And Danny had scattered some of his
school papers all over the room...
...and my husband grabbed his arm
to pull him away from them.
lt's just the sort of thing you do
1 00 times with a child...
...you know, in a park or in the street.
But on this particular occasion...
...my husband just used
too much strength...
...and he injured Danny's arm.
Anyway, something good did come out
of it all because he said:
"Wendy, I'm never going to
touch another drop.
And if l do, you can leave me."
And he didn't.
He hasn't had any alcohol in 5 months.
Boy.
We must really be high up.
The air feels so different.
Mm-hm.
Dad?
Yes?
l'm hungry.
You should've eaten your breakfast.
We'll get you something
as soon as we get to the hotel.
Okay, Mom.
Wasn't it around here that
the Donner party got snowbound?
l think that was farther west,
in the Sierras.
Oh.
What was the Donner party?
They were a party of settlers
in covered wagon times.
They got snowbound one winter
in the mountains.
They had to resort to cannibalism
in order to stay alive.
You mean they ate each other up?
They had to in order to survive.
Jack.
Don't worry, Mom.
l know all about cannibalism.
l saw it on TV.
See, it's okay.
He saw it on the television.
-What time does the plane leave?
-8:30.
That gives us plenty of time
to go over everything.
-Goodbye, Mr. Ullman.
-Bye.
Good morning. l hope you
haven't been waiting too long.
No problem. We had time
to grab a bite to eat.
Good. Glad you made it
before they shut down the kitchen.
-Hi.
-Is your family having a look around?
No, my son's
discovered the games room.
-Has your luggage been brought in?
-Right there.
Oh, fine.
ln view of all we have to cover today...
...l suggest we have a quick look
at your apartment and get started.
Have the Torrances' things
brought to their apartment.
-Fine.
-I'd better collect my family first.
Oh, yes.
This is our Colorado Lounge.
lt's beautiful.
My God!
This place is fantastic, isn't it, hon?
lt sure is.
l've never seen anything
like this before.
Are all these
lndian designs authentic?
l believe they're based...
...mainly on Navajo and Apache motifs.
They're really gorgeous.
As a matter of fact...
...this is probably the most
gorgeous hotel l've ever seen.
This old place has had
an illustrious past.
ln its heyday, it was a stopping
place for the jet setters...
...even before anybody knew
what a jet set was.
We had four presidents
who stayed here.
Lots of movie stars.
Royalty?
All the best people.
This is the staff wing of the hotel.
None of the other bedrooms
are heated during the winter.
-Goodbye, Mr. Ullman.
-Goodbye, girls.
ULLMAN:
And here are your quarters.
Living room, bedroom, bathroom.
And a small bedroom for your son.
Perfect for a child.
-Yeah.
-Yes.
ULLMAN: Well, then. Place is
very nicely self-contained.
Easy to keep.
Cozy.
ULLMAN:
Yes, very cozy for a family.
lf you feel like spreading out...
...you have the rest of the hotel
to move around in.
Well, it's very...
...homey.
Yeah.
This is our famous hedge maze.
lt's quite an attraction here.
The walls are 1 3 feet high...
...and the hedge is as old
as the hotel itself.
A lot of fun, but l wouldn't
want to go in there...
...unless l had an hour
to spare to find my way out.
WENDY:
When was the Overlook built?
Construction started in 1 907.
lt was finished in 1 909.
The site's supposed to be
on an Indian burial ground.
They actually had to repel...
...a few Indian attacks as they
were building it.
That's our Snowcat.
Can you both drive a car?
BOTH:
Yes.
ULLMAN: That's fine. Basically
the Snowcat operates very much like a car.
lt won't take you long
to get the hang of it.
As a matter of fact, we brought
a decorator in from Chicago...
...just last year to refurbish
this part of the hotel.
Oh. He sure did a beautiful job.
Pink and gold are my favorite colors.
Well, this is our Gold Ballroom.
Oh, l'll say!
We can accommodate up to
300 people here very comfortably.
Boy, we could really have
a good party in this room.
l'm afraid you won't do too well
here unless you brought supplies.
We remove the booze from
the premises when we shut down.
That reduces the insurance
we normally have to carry.
We don't drink.
Then you're in luck.
Dick, come on over and say hello
to Mr. and Mrs. Torrance.
This is Dick Hallorann,
our head chef.
Mr. Hallorann, l'm Jack.
This is my wife, Winifred.
Glad to meet you.
The Torrances will take care
of the Overlook this winter.
That's just great. How do you
folks like our hotel so far?
lt's just wonderful.
Hi, Danny!
l found him outside looking for you.
Dan, did you get tired
of bombing the universe?
Yeah.
Come on over here.
-Thanks.
-Thank you, Susie.
l think it'd be good if you could
show Mrs. Torrance the kitchen...
...while l continue on with Jack.
lt would be a pleasure. Right this way.
Great. See you later, hon.
Bye, darling.
Mrs. Torrance, your husband
introduced you as Winifred.
Now, are you a "Winnie,"
or a "Freddie"?
l'm a Wendy.
Oh, Wendy. That's nice.
That's the prettiest.
This is the kitchen, huh?
This is it.
How do you like it, Danny?
ls it big enough for you?
Yeah. lt's the biggest place l ever seen.
This whole place
is such an enormous maze.
l'll have to leave a trail of
breadcrumbs every time l come in.
Don't let it get you down.
lt's big, but it ain't
nothing but a kitchen.
A lot of this stuff
you'll never have to touch.
l wouldn't know
what to do with it if l did.
One thing for sure, you don't
have to worry about food.
You folks could eat here for a year
and never have the same menu twice.
Right here is our walk-in freezer.
This is where we keep
all of our meat.
You got 1 5 rib roasts...
...30 ten-pound bags of hamburger.
We got 1 2 turkeys,
about 40 chickens...
...50 sirloin steaks,
two dozen of pork roast...
...and 20 legs of lamb.
Do you like lamb, Doc?
-No.
-You don't?
What's your favorite food, then?
French fries and ketchup.
l think we can
manage that too, Doc.
Come along, now.
Watch your step.
Mr. Hallorann...
...how'd you know we call him Doc?
-Beg your pardon?
-Doc. You called Danny "Doc" twice.
-I did?
-Yeah.
We call him Doc sometimes,
like in the Bugs Bunny cartoons.
But how did you know?
l guess l probably
heard you call him that.
lt's possible.
But l honestly don't remember...
...calling him that
since we've been with you.
Anyway, he looks
like a Doc, doesn't he?
[lMlTATES BUGS BUNNY]
Eh, what's up, Doc?
Now, this is the storeroom.
ln here is where we keep...
...all the dried goods
and the canned goods.
We got canned fruits
and vegetables...
...canned fish and meats,
hot and cold cereals.
Post Toasties, Corn Flakes,
Sugar Puffs...
...Rice Krispies, oatmeal,
Wheatena and Cream of Wheat.
You got a dozen jugs
of black molasses.
We got 60 boxes of dried milk....
[lNAUDIBLE DlALOGUE]
DICK'S VOlCE:
How'd you like some ice cream, Doc?
DICK:
Sociables, finger rolls...
...and 7 kinds of what have you.
Now, we've got dried peaches,
dried apricots...
...dried raisins and dried prunes.
You know, you got to keep regular
if you want to be happy.
-Hi.
WENDY: Hi.
-How're you getting on?
-Fine.
Can we borrow Mrs. Torrance?
We're on our way to the basement.
l promise we won't
keep her very long.
No problem, Mr. Ullman. l was just
getting to the ice cream.
-You like ice cream, Doc?
-Yeah.
l thought you did.
You folks mind if l give Danny
some ice cream while we wait?
-Not at all.
-We don't mind.
-Good.
-Sound good to you, Doc?
DANNY: Yeah.
-Okay, you behave yourself.
What kind of ice cream do you like?
Chocolate.
Chocolate it shall be.
Come on, son.
lt's amazing, all this activity today.
The guests and some staff
left yesterday, but the...
...last day's always hectic.
Everybody wants to be on their way
as early as possible.
By 5:00 tonight, you'll never
know anybody was ever here.
WENDY: Just like a ghost ship, huh?
-Yes.
Do you know how l knew
your name was Doc?
You know what l'm talking about,
don't you?
l can remember when l was
a little boy...
...my grandmother and l
could hold conversations...
...entirely without ever
opening our mouths.
She called it "shining."
And for a long time l thought
it was just the two of us...
...that had "the shine" to us.
Just like you probably thought
you was the only one.
But there are other folks...
...though mostly they don't
know it, or don't believe it.
How long have you
been able to do it?
Why don't you want to talk about it?
l'm not supposed to.
Who says you ain't supposed to?
Tony.
Who's Tony?
Tony's the little boy
that lives in my mouth.
ls Tony the one that...
...tells you things?
Yes.
How does he tell you things?
lt's like l go to sleep,
and he shows me things.
But when l wake up,
l can't remember everything.
Does your mom and dad
know about Tony?
Yes.
Do they know he tells you things?
Tony told me never to tell them.
Has Tony ever told you
anything about this place?
About the Overlook Hotel?
l don't know.
Now think real hard, Doc.
Think.
Maybe he showed me something.
Try to think of what it was.
Mr. Hallorann, are you scared
of this place?
No.
Scared of nothing here.
lt's just that...
...you know, some places
are like people.
Some shine...
...and some don't.
l guess you could say
the Overlook Hotel...
...has something about it
that's like shining.
ls there something bad here?
Well...
...you know, Doc,
when something happens...
...it can leave a trace
of itself behind.
Say, like...
...if someone burns toast.
Well....
Maybe things that happen
leave other kind of traces behind.
Not things that anyone can notice.
But things that people
who shine can see.
Just like they can see things
that haven't happened yet...
...well...
...sometimes they can see things
that happened a long time ago.
l think a lot of things
happened right here...
...in this particular hotel
over the years.
And not all of them was good.
What about room 237?
Room 237?
You're scared of room 237, ain't you?
No, l ain't.
Mr. Hallorann, what is in room 237?
Nothing.
There ain't nothing in room 237.
But you ain't got no business
going in there anyway.
So stay out.
You understand? Stay out!
[WOLF HOWLS]
[KNOCKING]
Good morning, hon.
Your breakfast is ready.
What time is it?
lt's about 1 1 :30.
Eleven-thirty, Jesus.
l guess we've been
staying up too late.
l know it.
l made them just the way
you like them, sunny-side up.
Nice.
lt's really pretty outside.
How about taking me for a walk
after you finish your breakfast?
l suppose I ought to try
to do some writing first.
Any ideas yet?
Lots of ideas.
No good ones.
Something will come.
lt's just a matter of settling into
the habit of writing every day.
Yep. That's all it is.
lt's really nice up here, isn't it?
l love it.
l really do.
l've never been this happy
or comfortable anywhere.
lt's amazing how fast you get
used to such a big place.
l tell you, when we first
came up here...
...l thought it was kind of scary.
l fell in love with it right away.
When I came up here
for my interview...
...it was as though
l'd been here before.
l mean, we all have moments
of déjà vu...
...but this was ridiculous.
lt was almost as though l knew...
...what was going to be
around every corner.
Ooh-woo-ooh.
[THUDDlNG]
The loser has to keep
America clean. How's that?
-All right.
-And you're going to lose.
And l'm going to get you.
You'd better run fast!
[WENDY HUMS]
Look out!
l'm coming in close.
DANNY:
Loser has to keep America clean.
WENDY: Oh, no!
DANNY: Keep America clean.
Okay. Danny, you win.
Let's take the rest of this walking.
-Okay.
-Whew.
Give me your hand.
lsn't it beautiful?
Yeah.
DANNY:
Dead end.
WENDY:
Woo, we made it.
-Isn't it beautiful?
DANNY: Yeah.
lt's so pretty.
Yeah.
l didn't think it was
going to be this big. Did you?
Nope.
WOMAN [ON TV]:
Rutherford was serving a life sentence...
...for a 1 968 shooting.
And the search continues
for that missing Aspen woman.
Twenty-four-year-old Susan Robertson
has been missing 1 0 days.
She disappeared on a hunting trip
with her husband.
They may have to
call off the search...
...if a predicted snowstorm
moves in tomorrow.
lt's so beautiful
in Denver today...
...it's hard to believe
a snowstorm could be close.
l want to go outside
and lie in the sun...
...yet to our north, to our west,
it is snowing and cold.
And it's moving...
...right here towards Colorado
as we talk. It's incredible.
[TYPEWRlTER KEYS CLACKlNG]
Hi, hon.
How's it going?
Fine.
Get a lot written today?
Yes.
Hey, the weather forecast
said it's going to snow tonight.
What do you want me to do about it?
Come on, hon.
Don't be so grouchy.
l'm not...
...being grouchy.
l just want to finish my work.
Okay. l understand.
l'll come back later
with a couple of sandwiches.
Maybe you'll let me
read something then.
Wendy...
...let me explain something to you.
When you come in and interrupt,
you're breaking my concentration.
You're distracting me...
...and it will then take me time
to get back to where l was.
Understand?
Yeah.
Fine.
We're going to make a new rule:
Whenever I'm in here...
...and you hear me typing...
[PUNCHES KEYS]
...or whatever the fuck
you hear me doing in here...
...when l'm in here,
that means l am working.
That means don't come in.
Now, do you think
you can handle that?
Yeah.
Fine.
Why don't you start right now
and get the fuck out of here?
Okay.
[DANNY LAUGHlNG]
WENDY:
All right, you!
l know you've got more.
DANNY:
Missed!
Don't have!
No fair anymore.
[TYPEWRlTER KEYS CLACKlNG]
Oh, no.
l knew it.
This is KDK 12 calling KDK 1 .
KDK 1 2 to KDK 1 .
This is KDK 1 .
We're receiving you. Over.
Hi, this is Wendy Torrance
at the Overlook Hotel.
Hi, how are you folks
getting on up there? Over.
We're just fine.
But our telephones
aren't doing too well.
Are the lines down,
by any chance? Over.
Yes, quite a few of them are down
due to the storm. Over.
Any chance of them
being repaired soon? Over.
Well, I wouldn't like to say.
Most winters they stay that way
until spring. Over.
Boy, this storm is really something,
isn't it? Over.
Yes. lt's one of the worst
we've had for years.
ls there anything else we can
do for you, Mrs. Torrance?
l suppose not. Over.
lf you folks have any problems
up there, just give us a call.
And, Mrs. Torrance?
lt might be a good idea if you
leave your radio on all the time.
Okay. We'll do that.
lt was real nice talking to you.
Bye. Over and out.
GlRLS:
Hello, Danny.
Come and play with us.
Come and play with us, Danny.
Forever...
...and ever...
...and ever.
Tony...
...l'm scared.
Remember what Mr. Hallorann said.
It's just like pictures in a book, Danny.
lt isn't real.
Please let me give you some money.
l wouldn't think of it.
Well, how can l repay you?
It's okay. Really.
Well, l'm going to have some coffee.
Would you like some?
Sure.
Great. Sit down.
Ooh, marvelous doughnuts.
Help yourself.
-Coffee will be ready--
DANNY: Mom.
WENDY:
Yeah.
DANNY: Can l go up to my room
and get my fire engine?
WENDY:
Not right now. Daddy's asleep.
DANNY:
l won't make any noise.
WENDY:
Now come on, Doc.
He only went to bed a few hours ago.
Can't you wait till later?
DANNY: l won't make a sound.
l promise l'll tiptoe.
WENDY:
Well, all right.
But really don't make a sound.
DANNY:
l won't, Mom.
Make sure you come right back...
...because l'm going to
make lunch soon.
-Okay?
DANNY: Okay, Mom.
Can l go to my room
and get my fire engine?
Come here for a minute first.
How's it going, Doc?
Okay.
Having a good time?
Yes, Dad.
Good.
l want you to have a good time.
l am, Dad.
Dad?
Yes?
Do you feel bad?
No.
l'm just a little bit tired.
Then why don't you go to sleep?
l can't.
l got too much to do.
Dad?
Yes?
Do you like this hotel?
Yes.
l do.
l love it.
Don't you?
l guess so.
Good.
l want you to like it here.
l wish we could stay here forever...
...and ever...
...and ever.
Dad?
What?
You would never hurt Mommy or me,
would you?
What do you mean?
Did your mother ever say that to you?
That l would hurt you?
No, Dad.
You sure?
Yes, Dad.
l love you, Danny.
l love you more than anything else...
...in the whole world...
...and l would never do anything
to hurt you...
...never.
You know that, don't you?
-Hm?
-Yes, Dad.
Good.
[WlND HOWLlNG]
[DANNY lMlTATlNG ENGINE NOlSES]
Mom?
Mom, are you in there?
[JACK SCREAMlNG]
[JACK GROANS]
[JACK SCREAMS]
WENDY:
Jack!
Jack? Jack!
What happened?
Honey...
...what's wrong?
Jack?
l had the most...
...terrible nightmare l ever had.
-It was the most horrible dream.
-It's okay, it's okay now.
Really.
l dreamed that l...
...that l killed you and Danny.
But l didn't just kill you.
l cut you up into little pieces.
My God.
l must be losing my mind.
Everything's going to be all right.
Come on. Let's get up off the floor.
lt's okay. There. Now sit up.
lt's okay.
Danny!
Everything's okay!
Just go play in your room for a while.
Your dad's just got a headache.
Danny, mind what l say.
Go play in your room.
Honey, let me just go
get him out of here.
l'll be right back.
Danny.
Why don't you mind me?
Oh, Danny.
Oh, my God.
What happened to your neck?
Danny, what happened to your neck?
Huh?
You did this to him...
...didn't you?!
You son of a bitch!
You did this to him!
Didn't you?!
How could you?!
Oh.
[GROANlNG]
God! l'd give anything for a drink.
l'd give my goddamn soul...
...for just a glass of beer.
Hi, Lloyd.
A little slow tonight, isn't it?
Yes, it is, Mr. Torrance.
What will it be?
l'm awfully glad
you asked me that, Lloyd...
...because l just happen to have
two twenties...
...and two tens
right here in my wallet.
l was afraid they were
going to be there until next April.
So here's what:
You slip me a bottle of bourbon...
...a little glass and some ice.
You can do that, can't you, Lloyd?
You're not too busy, are you?
No, sir. l'm not busy at all.
Good man.
You set them up...
...and l'll knock them back,
one by one.
White man's burden, Lloyd, my man.
White man's burden.
Say, Lloyd...
...it seems l'm temporarily light.
How's my credit in this joint, anyway?
Your credit's fine, Mr. Torrance.
That's swell.
l like you, Lloyd.
l always liked you.
You were always the best of them.
Best goddamned bartender...
...from Timbuktu to Portland, Maine.
Or Portland, Oregon, for that matter.
Thank you for saying so.
Here's to five miserable months
on the wagon...
...and all the irreparable harm
that it's caused me.
How are things going, Mr. Torrance?
Things could be better.
Things could be
a whole lot better.
l hope it's nothing serious.
No.
Nothing serious.
Just a little problem with...
...the old sperm bank upstairs.
Nothing I can't handle, though.
Thanks.
Women.
Can't live with them...
...can't live without them.
Words of wisdom, Lloyd.
Words of...
...wisdom.
l never laid a hand on him,
goddamn it.
l didn't.
l wouldn't touch one hair
on his goddamn little head.
l love the little son of a bitch.
l'd do anything for him.
Any fucking thing for him.
But that bitch!
As long as I live...
...she'll never let me forget
what happened.
l did hurt him once, okay?
lt was an accident.
Completely unintentional.
lt could have happened to anybody.
And it was three goddamn years ago!
The little fucker had thrown all my
papers all over the floor.
All I tried to do was pull him up.
A momentary loss of
muscular coordination.
l mean...
...a few extra foot-pounds of energy...
...per second, per second.
WENDY:
Jack!
Oh, Jack.
Thank God you're here.
Jack.
There's someone else
in the hotel with us.
There's a crazy woman
in one of the rooms.
She tried to strangle Danny.
Are you out of your fucking mind?
No.
lt's the truth! Really.
l swear it. Danny told me.
He went up into one of the bedrooms.
The door was open, and he saw this
crazy woman in the bathtub.
She tried to strangle him!
Which room was it?
[MUSlC PLAYS ON TV]
NEWS NARRATOR:
From Channel 1 0 in Miami...
...this is Newswatch
with Glenn Rinker...
...Ann Bishop, and
the award-winning Newswatch team.
Good evening. l'm Glenn Rinker,
Newswatch Ten.
As Miami continues to swelter
in a record winter heat wave...
...bringing temperatures to the 90s...
...Central and Mountain states
are buried in snow.
In Colorado, 1 0 inches of snow
fell in just a few hours tonight.
Travel in the Rockies
is almost impossible.
Airports are shut down, stranding
thousands of passengers.
Highways are blocked
by snowdrifts.
Railroad tracks are frozen.
Officials in Colorado
tell Newswatch...
...at least three have been killed
by exposure to freezing winds.
The governor of Colorado is expected...
...to declare a weather emergency.
The National Guard
might be called out...
...to clear streets and roads.
Weather forecasters
predict more snow...
...and heavy winds
tonight and tomorrow...
...with temperatures dropping
well below zero.
Back here in Florida,
we've got the opposite problem.
The heat and humidity
are supposed to climb.
Local beaches should be jammed.
Our weather expert,
Walter Cronice...
...will have the local forecast
later on Newswatch.
[HEART THUDDlNG]
[WOMAN CACKLlNG]
[RlNGlNG]
MAN [ON RECORDING]: We're sorry.
Your call cannot be completed as dialed.
lf you need assistance,
please call the operator.
[KNOCKING]
Jack?
JACK:
Yes, it's me.
Thank God.
Did you find anything?
No. Nothing at all.
l didn't see one goddamn thing.
You went into the room Danny said?
To 237?
Yes, l did.
And you didn't see anything at all?
Absolutely nothing.
How is he?
He's still asleep.
Good.
l'm sure he'll be himself again
in the morning.
Are you sure it was the right room?
l mean, maybe Danny made a mistake.
He must have gone in that room.
The door was open,
the lights were on.
l just don't understand it.
What about those bruises on his neck?
Somebody did that to him.
l think...
...he did it to himself.
No.
That's not possible.
Wendy...
...once you rule out his version
of what happened...
...there is no other explanation.
ls there?
lt wouldn't be that different
from the episode...
...that he had before
we came up here.
Would it?
[WENDY CRlES]
WENDY:
Oh, Jack.
Whatever the explanation is...
...I think we...
...have to get Danny out of here.
Get him out of here?
Yes.
You mean...
...just leave the hotel?
Yes.
JACK:
lt is so...
...typical of you to create
a problem like this...
...when l finally have a chance
to accomplish something!
When I'm really into my work!
l could really write my own ticket
if l went back now, couldn't I?
Shoveling out driveways,
work in a car wash.
-Any of that appeal to you?
-Jack...
Wendy, l have let you fuck up my life
so far...
...but l am not going to let you
fuck this up.
[CAN RATTLING]
[BALLROOM MUSlC PLAYlNG]
[RlNGlNG]
MAN [ON PHONE]:
Good evening. Forest Service.
Hello, my name is Dick Hallorann.
l'm the head chef at
the Overlook Hotel.
Good evening.
What can l do for you?
l've been trying to make
an urgent phone call up there...
...but the operator said
that the phone lines are down.
A lot of lines around here
are down due to the storm.
l hate to put you through
any trouble...
...but there's a family up there
all by themselves with a young kid.
And with this storm
and everything...
...l'd appreciate it if you'd give
them a call on your radio...
...just to see if everything's okay.
l'll be glad to do that.
Why don't you call me back
in about 20 minutes?
Thank you very much.
l'll do that.
All right, sir.
[BALLROOM MUSlC PLAYS]
[PEOPLE CHATTERlNG AND LAUGHlNG]
Good evening, Mr. Torrance.
Good evening.
Hi, Lloyd.
Been away, but now I'm back.
Good evening, Mr. Torrance.
lt's good to see you.
lt's good to be back, Lloyd.
What'll it be, sir?
Hair of the dog that bit me.
Bourbon on the rocks.
That'll do her.
No charge to you, Mr. Torrance.
No charge?
Your money's no good here.
Orders from the house.
Drink up, Mr. Torrance.
l'm the kind of man likes to know
who's buying their drinks, Lloyd.
lt's not a matter that concerns you,
Mr. Torrance.
At least, not at this point.
Anything you say, Lloyd.
Anything you say.
Oh!
Oh, dear! I'm so sorry, sir.
-Oh.
-Oh, dear. Oh, dear.
l've made an awful mess
of your jacket, sir.
Oh, that's all right.
l've got plenty ofjackets.
l'm afraid it's advocaat, sir.
lt tends to stain.
Advocaat, is it?
Yes, sir. I think the best thing...
...is to come along
to the gentlemen's room...
...and we'll get
some water to it, sir.
Looks like you might have got a
spot of it on yourself...
...Jeevesy old boy.
That doesn't matter, sir.
You're the important one.
Awfully nice of you to say.
Of course, l intended to change
my jacket this evening...
...before the fish and goose soiree.
Very wise, sir. Very wise.
JACK:
Here. l'll just...
...hold this for you there,
Jeevesy.
Thank you, sir. Thank you.
Let's see if we can improve this
with a little water, sir.
All right. l'll just...
...set my bourbon and advocaat
down right there.
Won't keep you a moment.
Fine.
What do they call you, Jeevesy?
Grady, sir. Delbert Grady.
Grady?
Yes, sir.
Delbert Grady.
That's right, sir.
Uh....
Mr. Grady...
...haven't l seen you
somewhere before?
Why, no, sir. I don't believe so.
lt's coming off now, sir.
Uh...
...Mr. Grady...
...weren't you once
the caretaker here?
Why, no, sir. I don't believe so.
You a married man, are you, Mr. Grady?
Yes, sir.
l have a wife and two daughters, sir.
And...
...where are they now?
They're somewhere around.
l'm not quite sure at the moment.
Mr. Grady.
You were the caretaker here.
l recognize you.
l saw your picture
in the newspapers.
You...
...chopped your wife and daughter
up into little bits.
And...
...then you blew your brains out.
That's strange, sir.
l don't have any recollection
of that at all.
Mr. Grady...
...you were the caretaker here.
l'm sorry to differ with you, sir.
But you...
...are the caretaker.
You've always been the caretaker.
l should know, sir.
l've always been here.
Did you know, Mr. Torrance...
...that your son...
...is attempting to bring
an outside party...
...into this situation?
Did you know that?
No.
He is, Mr. Torrance.
Who?
A nigger.
A nigger?
A nigger...
...cook.
How?
Your son...
...has a very great talent.
l don't think you are aware
how great it is.
But he is attempting to use
that very talent...
...against your will.
Well...
...he is a very willful boy.
lndeed he is, Mr. Torrance.
A very willful boy.
A rather...
...naughty boy...
...if l may be so bold, sir.
lt's his mother.
She...
...interferes.
Perhaps they need a good...
...talking-to.
lf...
...you don't mind my saying so.
Perhaps...
...a bit more.
My girls, sir...
...they didn't care for
the Overlook at first.
One of them actually stole
a pack of matches...
...and tried to burn it down.
But l...
...corrected them, sir.
And when my wife tried to prevent me
from doing my duty...
...l...
...corrected her.
We have the Snowcat.
lf the weather breaks...
...we might just be able...
...to get down the mountain.
[HEART THUDDlNG]
l could call
the forest rangers first...
...and...
...tell them that we're coming...
...so that...
...they could start searching
for us in case we didn't make it.
And if Jack won't come with us...
...l'll just have to tell him that
we're going by ourselves.
That's all there is to it.
DANNY [lN TONY'S VOlCE]:
Redrum.
Redrum. Redrum.
-Danny?
-Redrum.
Redrum. Redrum.
-What's the matter, hon?
Redrum!
Are you having a bad dream?
Danny?
Hon?
Danny's not here, Mrs. Torrance.
Come on, hon.
Wake up.
You just had a bad dream.
Everything's okay.
Danny can't wake up, Mrs. Torrance.
Danny.
Wake up!
Come on.
Right now.
Wake up!
Danny's gone away, Mrs. Torrance.
Danny.
MAN [OVER RADlO]:
This is KDK 1 calling KDK 1 2.
KDK 1 calling KDK 1 2.
Are you receiving me?
This is KDK 1 calling KDK 1 2.
KDK 1 calling KDK 1 2.
Do you read me?
This is KDK 1 calling KDK 1 2.
KDK 1 calling KDK 1 2.
Are you receiving me?
This is KDK 1 calling KDK 1 2.
KDK 1 calling KDK 1 2.
Do you read me?
This is KDK 1 calling KDK 1 2.
KDK 1 calling KDK 1 2.
Are you receiv--
[RADIO SHUTS OFF]
[RlNGlNG]
MAN:
Good evening. Forest service.
This is Dick Hallorann again.
l called a while ago about
the folks at the Overlook Hotel.
Oh, yeah.
We tried to contact them several
times but they didn't answer.
Maybe they got their radio
turned off or they can't hear it.
lf you'd like, l'd be glad
to try again later on.
That's very nice of you.
l'll call you back later.
Bye.
Pardon me, miss.
What time will we get to Denver?
We're due to arrive at 8:20, sir.
Thank you very much.
[TYPEWRlTER KEYS CLACKlNG]
[PHONE RlNGlNG]
Durkin's Garage.
DICK:
Can I speak to Larry?
Speaking.
Hi, Larry. This is Dick.
Dick Hallorann.
Dick! How you doing?
How's the weather down there?
l'm not in Florida.
l'm calling from Stapleton Airport.
What are you doing there?
l just got in from Miami.
l got to get to the Overlook today.
What's the weather like there?
The snowplows are keeping things
moving in town...
...but the mountain roads
are blocked.
Then l'm going to need a Snowcat
to get up there.
Can you fix me up with one?
What's the big deal
about getting there today...
...especially in this weather?
Larry, just between you and me,
we got a very serious problem...
...with the people taking care
of the place.
They turned out to be
completely unreliable assholes.
Ullman phoned me last night.
And l'm supposed to find out
if they have to be replaced.
How long will it take you
to get here?
About five hours.
l'm going to rent a car
here at the airport.
Okay, l'll take care of it.
Thanks, Larry.
l really appreciate that.
That's all right. Drive carefully.
[MUSlC PLAYS ON RADlO]
HAL: You're with Hal and Charlie
on Radio 63, KHOW, Denver.
And we have a bad day out there.
CHARLlE: Heavy snow throughout
the Denver metro area.
Many mountain passes...
...Wolf Creek and Red Mountain
passes are closed...
...and the chain law is in effect
at the Eisenhower Tunnel.
HAL:
We hear from the news department...
...only a few flights are
landing at Stapleton Airport...
...and with storms like this...
...I guess the entire airport will
be closed within the hour.
CHARLIE: The storm will continue through
the day and the Weather Service...
...has declared a stockman's
and traveler's advisory...
...for all areas outlying
the Denver metro region.
Get the cows in the barn.
[MUSlC PLAYS ON TV]
Hon?
Listen to me for a minute, will you?
l'm just going to go and
talk to Daddy for a few minutes...
...and l'll be right back.
l want you to just stay here...
...and watch your cartoons, okay?
Okay, hon?
Yes, Mrs. Torrance.
All right.
l'll-- l'll be back
in just about five minutes.
l'm going to lock the door
behind me.
Jack?
JACK:
How do you like it?
[SHRIEKS]
Jack.
How do you like it?
What are you doing down here?
l just...
...wanted...
...to talk to you.
Okay.
Let's talk.
What do you want to talk about?
l....
l can't really remember.
You can't remember.
No...
...l can't.
JACK:
Maybe it was about Danny?
Maybe it was about him.
I think we should discuss Danny.
l think...
...we should discuss
what should be done with him.
What should be done with him?
l don't know.
l don't think that's true.
l think you have some
very definite ideas...
...about what should be done
with Danny.
And l'd like to know
what they are.
Well, I...
...l think maybe he should be taken
to a doctor.
You think "maybe"
he should be taken to a doctor?
Yes.
When do you think "maybe"
he should be taken to a doctor?
As soon as possible?
[lN HlGH-PlTCHED VOlCE]
"As soon as possible?"
Please.
You believe his health
might be at stake.
Yes.
And you are concerned about him.
And are you concerned about me?
Of course l am.
Of course you are!
Have you ever thought about
my responsibilities?
What are you talking about?
Have you ever had
a single moment's...
...thought about
my responsibilities?
Have you ever thought
for a single moment...
...about my responsibilities
to my employers?!
Has it ever occurred to you...
...that l have agreed to look after
the hotel until May 1 st?
Does it matter to you at all...
...that the owners have placed
their complete confidence in me...
...and that l have signed
a letter of agreement...
...in which l've accepted
that responsibility?
Do you have the slightest idea...
...what a moral and ethical
principal is? Do you?!
Has it ever occurred to you what
would happen to my future...
...if l fail to live up to
my responsibilities?
Has it ever occurred to you?
Has it?!
Stay away from me!
Why?
l just want to go back to my room.
Well...
...l'm very confused.
And l just need a chance
to think things over.
You've had your whole fucking life
to think things over!
What good's a few minutes more
going to do you now?
Stay away from me!
Please!
Don't hurt me.
l'm not going to hurt you.
Stay away from me!
-Wendy.
-Stay away!
Darling.
Light of my life.
l'm not going to hurt you.
You didn't let me finish
my sentence.
l said, "l'm not going to hurt you."
l'm just going to bash
your brains in.
l'm going to bash them
right the fuck in.
Stay away from me!
Don't hurt me!
l'm not going to hurt you.
Stay away from me!
Stay away!
Please!
Stop swinging the bat.
Stay away from me.
Put that bat down, Wendy.
Stop it!
Wendy.
Give me the bat.
Please!
-Stay away!
-Give me the bat.
Stop it!
-Jack.
-Stay away from me.
-Stop swinging the bat.
Please stop!
Give me the bat.
-Stay away from me.
-Wendy.
-Stop it!
-Give me the bat.
-Stay away!
Ah! Goddamn--!
[WENDY CRlES]
[GROANlNG]
What are you doing?
Hey.
Wait a minute.
What are you doing?
Oh! Oh!
JACK:
Wait a minute!
[BANGlNG ON DOOR]
What are you doing?
Open the door!
Goddamn it!
Let me out of here!
Open the goddamn door!
Wendy, listen.
Let me out and l'll forget
the whole goddamn thing.
lt'll be just like nothing ever happened.
Wendy, baby.
l think you hurt my head real bad.
l'm dizzy.
l need a doctor.
Honey.
Don't leave me in here.
l'm going to go now.
l'm going to try...
...to get Danny down
the Sidewinder...
...in the Snowcat today.
l'll bring back a doctor.
Wendy.
WENDY:
l'm going to go now.
Wendy.
Yes.
You've got a big surprise
coming to you.
You're not going anywhere.
Go check out the Snowcat and the
radio, and you'll see what l mean.
[JACK LAUGHlNG]
Go check it out.
Go check it out!
[GRUNTING]
[KNOCKING]
Wendy?
GRADY:
lt's Grady, Mr. Torrance.
Delbert Grady.
Grady?
Oh, Grady.
Grady, uh....
Hello, Grady.
Mr. Torrance...
...l see you can hardly
have taken care of the...
...business we discussed.
No need to rub it in, Mr. Grady.
l'll deal with that situation
as soon as l get out of here.
Will you indeed, Mr. Torrance?
l wonder.
l have my doubts.
l, and others, have come to believe...
...that your heart is not in this.
That you haven't the belly for it.
Just give me one more chance
to prove it, Mr. Grady.
That's all l ask.
Your wife appears to be stronger
than we imagined, Mr. Torrance.
Somewhat more...
...resourceful.
She seems to have got
the better of you.
For the moment, Mr. Grady.
Only for the moment.
l fear you will have to deal
with this matter...
...in the harshest possible way,
Mr. Torrance.
l fear...
...that is the only thing to do.
There's nothing l look forward to...
...with greater pleasure, Mr. Grady.
You give your word on that,
do you, Mr. Torrance?
l give you my word.
[LOCK OPENS]
Redrum.
Redrum. Redrum!
-Ah!
-Redrum! Redrum! Redrum!
Danny, stop it!
Redrum!
[THUDDlNG AT DOOR]
Wendy, l'm home.
Come out, come out,
wherever you are.
Danny...
...l can't get out.
Run!
Run and hide!
Quick!
Little pigs, little pigs, let me come in.
Not by the hair
on your chinny-chin-chin?
Then l'll huff...
...and l'll puff...
...and l'll blow your house in!
[WENDY SCREAMlNG]
Please!
Don't!
Stop it!
Here's Johnny!
Ah!
[SNOWCAT ENGlNE RUMBLlNG]
DICK:
Hello?
Anybody here?
[YELLS]
[DlCK AND DANNY SCREAM]
Danny!
Danny-boy!
Danny?
Danny.
[PEOPLE CHANTlNG]
Danny!
l'm coming!
l'm coming, Dan!
Danny?
[SHRIEKS]
Great party, isn't it?
JACK:
Danny!
l'm coming!
You can't get away!
l'm right behind you!
[WENDY SCREAMS]
[GlGGLING]
Danny!
-Mommy!
-Danny, come here!
Mommy.
[THlCKLY]
Danny!
Where...?
[GROANlNG]
[SNOWCAT ENGlNE SPUTTERlNG]
[ENGINE ROARS]
[YELLING lNCOHERENTLY]
[BALLROOM MUSlC PLAYlNG]